

SRM Institute of Science and Technology, Kattankulathur, Tamil Nadu, India — IN 603203

M +91 8860896000

E <u>arizsiddiqui@hotmail.com</u>
W <u>www.arizsiddiqui.tech</u>

L @arizsiddiqui

Profile

I am an experienced developer and manager with a demonstrated history of working in the computer industry. I am an individual with strong communication and inter-personal skills, having successfully contributed to team success with hard-work, attention-to-detail and leadership qualities. I am also currently developing my management skills in various domains of the technology industry.

Experience

Committee Head, Aaruush – 2019 – Present

Helped organise one of the largest techno-management fests in South India, playing decisive roles in guest invitation and itinerary management. Personally tended to high-profile guests and successfully managed crisis situations.

Associate Technical Lead, Microsoft Learn Student Ambassadors SRM – 2019—Present Completed multiple projects under the banner of the Technical Team of the club, including a NLP based browser extension, a CLI for keeping API and OAuth Tokens safe and a webinar on the basics of Python. Currently working towards nurturing and developing talented yet inexperienced developers.

Head Boy, Nirmal Bhartia School - 2018-2019

Served as the head of the Student Council of the school, helping implement regulations that improved the school life of the students.

Web Developer, IN-X Union – 2016—2017

Served as a web developer for the school IT Club in Secondary School. Helped organise and manage the techfest Infoyage for 2 years.

Education

SRM Institute of Science and Technology, Kattankulathur, Tamil Nadu

B.Tech. Computer Science and Engineering (2019—2023)

Nirmal Bhartia School, Sector 14, Dwarka, New Delhi

Senior Secondary School (2017-2019)

Skills

Technical

Python, C, C++, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, Swift, SQL, Git, OpenCV, TensorFlow, Numpy, Pandas, Bootstrap, Scikit-learn, Scipy, Keras.

Management

Communication, Leadership, Attention to detail, Quick learner, Delivers under pressure, Team worker.